<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<articles>
  <article>
    <id>additions-005</id>
    <title>MAS Consolidation Phase 2 is coming to eOffer/eMod</title>
    <date>2020-01-17</date>
    <summary><![CDATA[
      <p>During late January/early February 2020, GSA will be implementing Phase 2 of MAS Consolidation.  These changes will impact the way you interact with the system.</p>
      <a href="index.html#article_article_page/additions-005">Read More</a>
    ]]></summary>
    <body><![CDATA[
      <p>Throughout the end of January and into early February 2020, GSA will be implementing MAS Consolidation Phase 2 to all contracts. GSA modernized federal acquisition by consolidating the existing 24 Schedules into one single Schedule for products, services, and solutions. This will provide consistency in the program for all stakeholders, make it easier for customers to find total solutions under one contract vehicle, ensure terms and conditions meet the needs of our customers, and eliminate duplicate contracts.</p>
      <p>Phase 2 is a continuation of the initial MAS Consolidation updates implemented during the last quarter of 2019. It will affect current Schedule contract holders and will also affect the Mass Mod and eMod systems. During this phase, you will still have the ability to update your contract, and the ability to process Add SIN and Delete SIN modifications has been reinstated.  During the initial Mass Mod phase, GSA removed the add/delete SIN function to ensure that all modifications would be processed prior to the Mass Mod acceptance. The functionality has since been restored.</p>
      <p>In order to be prepared for this update, there are a few things that you are able to do:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Review the new solicitation (47QSMD20R0001) on <a href="https://beta.sam.gov/" >beta.sam.gov</a></li>
        <li>Ensure you have joined the MAS Community on <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/tag/mas">Interact</a></li>
        <li>Send questions to <a href="mailto:maspmo@gsa.gov">maspmo@gsa.gov</a></li>
        <li>Review the new SIN structure and the mapping legacy structure on the <a href="https://www.gsa.gov/buying-selling/purchasing-programs/gsa-schedules/selling-through-schedules/roadmap-for-new-schedule-offerors/1-get-ready/available-offerings-and-requirements">Available Offerings and Requirements</a> page</li>
      </ul>
    ]]></body>
  </article>
  <article>
    <id>additions-004</id>
    <title>MAS Consolidation is now live in eOffer/eMod</title>
    <date>2019-11-09</date>
    <summary><![CDATA[
      <p>On October 01, 2019 GSA implemented new Consolidated Scheduling.  These changes will impact how you interact with the system.</p>
      <a href="index.html#article_article_page/additions-004">Read More</a>
    ]]></summary>
    <body><![CDATA[
      <p>On October 01, 2019, GSA implemented MAS Consolidation to all contracts.  GSA modernized federal acquisition by consolidating the existing 24 Schedules into one single Schedule for products, services, and solutions.  This will provide consistency in the program for all stakeholders, make it easier for customers to find total solutions under one contract vehicle, ensure terms and conditions meet the needs of our customers, and eliminate duplicate contracts.</p>
      <p>Businesses with existing contracts are able to process modifications, accept orders and are still required to maintain compliance with the current terms and conditions of their contracts. Users are able to prepare new offers under the Consolidated MAS schedule, but no new contract awards will be made under this schedule until after January 1, 2020.  User guides are being updated to incorporate the new changes.</p>
      <p>For more information, visit the <a href="https://interact.gsa.gov/document/want-know-more-about-mas-consolidation">MAS Interact Page</a> or view our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gPydy_f-p-w">MAS Consolidation training webinar</a> for more information.</p>

    ]]></body>
  </article>
  <article>
    <id>additions-003</id>
    <title>Name Change Agreement Process</title>
    <date>2019-08-23</date>
    <summary><![CDATA[
      <p>Follow the correct steps during a Change of Name Agreement Modification in order to ensure contract integrity.</p>
      <a href="index.html#article_article_page/additions-003">Read More</a>
    ]]></summary>
    <body><![CDATA[
      <p>The Change of Name Agreement process can be a little confusing and could potentially effect the way the contract is handled if you do not execute the process correctly.  In order to assist you, we added additional guidance that should answer any questions you may have.</p>
      <p>The Change of Name Agreement process has multiple steps in order to submit the modification successfully.  We have added a simple workflow that outlines where and when to update company information.  You can find the workflow in the <a href="index.html#book_page_page/modules%2Fbook%2Fdatabase.xml/eoffer_emod/emod-resources/modtypes/legal-modifications/change-of-name-agreement-modification">Change of Name Agreement eMod</a> section.</p>
      <p>Additionally, it is important to note that if you do not follow the guidance or try and proceed through the Change of Name Agreement process without the proper steps being taken, you risk being completely locked out of all systems.  By first going to D&B and updating your company name, SAM will automatically be notified and you will just need to accept that change.  Then, once you receive the email from GSA, you will then be allowed to submit the needed modification(s) successfully.</p>
    ]]></body>
  </article>
  <article>
    <id>additions-002</id>
    <title><![CDATA[Release of the eOffer/eMod Online User Guide]]></title>
    <date>2014-02-01</date>
    <summary><![CDATA[
      <p>The new version of the Online User Guide has launched. Learn more about its features here.</p>
      <a href="index.html#article_article_page/additions-002">Read More</a>
    ]]></summary>
    <body><![CDATA[
      <p>The new version of the Online User Guide has launched. Learn more about its features here.</p>
      <h4>The Side Navigation Menu</h4>
      <hr/>
      <p>Open the navigation menu by clicking the menu button in the top left corner of the screen. You will be able to access this menu at all times.</p>
      <div class="screenshotContainer">
        <div class="screenshotBox">
          <a class="fancybox" data-lightbox="additions-002" href="images/002-NavMenu.jpg" title=" ">
            <img src="images/002-NavMenu.jpg" alt="The navigation is anchored in the top left" delegate="" button="" is="" class="screenshot"/>
          </a>
          <div class="screenshotText">
            <p class="figCaption">The navigation menu is anchored in the top left corner of the screen.</p>
            <p class="clickTo">Click the image to enlarge</p>
          </div>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div class="screenshotContainer">
        <div class="screenshotBox">
          <a class="fancybox" data-lightbox="additions-002" href="images/002-NavMenuOpen.jpg" title=" ">
            <img src="images/002-NavMenuOpen.jpg" alt="A look at the eOffer/eMod User Guide with the navigation menu open." delegate="" button="" is="" class="screenshot"/>
          </a>
          <div class="screenshotText">
            <p class="figCaption">A look at the eOffer/eMod User Guide with the navigation menu open.</p>
            <p class="clickTo">Click the image to enlarge</p>
          </div>
        </div>
      </div>
      <p>You can search the User Guide by using the search fields located at the top of the navigation menu, as well as at the top right of the page header. There is also an <a href="index.html#search_page_block/data%2Fbooks_index.json//0/20">Advanced Search</a> feature located under the <strong>Utilities</strong> section.</p>
      <div class="screenshotContainer">
        <div class="screenshotBox">
          <a class="fancybox" data-lightbox="additions-002" href="images/002-Search.jpg" title=" ">
            <img src="images/002-Search.jpg" alt="These search fields are the quickest way to search the User Guide." delegate="" button="" is="" class="screenshot"/>
          </a>
          <div class="screenshotText">
            <p class="figCaption">These search fields are the quickest way to search the User Guide.</p>
            <p class="clickTo">Click the image to enlarge</p>
          </div>
        </div>
      </div>
    ]]></body>
  </article>
</articles>